### **SUMMARY**

I design & develop cross-platform software with a focus on clear visual communication, natural user input, and trend-agnostic, painless product experiences. From wireframe, to alpha release, to multi-variant testing & analytics I welcome collaborative critique and deliver features & requests promptly.

My diverse background enables me to architect custom, holistic solutions to each project that cater to the unique and evolving needs of both client & end-user.

# **PROFICIENCY**

### Development

HTML5, CSS3, SASS, PHP
ES5, ES6, Node, Electron, Npm, JSON
Babel, Express, Handlebars, Jquery
Phaser, Moment, Bluebird, Nodemailer
Linux Servers, AWS, Digital Ocean
MacOS, Windows
C#, Bash, Git, Svn
Apache, Jenkins, REST, SSH, SSL

#### **Project Management**

Pivotal, Jira, Trello, Asana, Slack MS/Libre/Open Offices

#### **Design & Animation**

Photoshop, Illustrator InvisionApp, Sketch, Gliffy After Effects, Premiere, FCPX Unity3D, Maya

## **Marketing & Testing**

Google Analytics Adwords, Tag Manager Mailchimp, Campaign Monitor Salesforce, Hubspot, Insightly Visual Website Optimizer CrazyEgg, Mouseflow

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Front-End Developer, Designer, Animator - Mursion, Inc.

May 2016 - Present

Develop interactive wireframes and lead UX/design planning for emerging mobile, web, and native software. Work with the software dev, and art teams to produce responsive web front-ends and Unity3D UIs - from video recording analytics, to session booking management, to system verification, to session launch dashboard & simulation control HUD.

Guide offshore team for design standards and software interfacing, consult with sales team for new lead generation, SEO, analytics, CRM, email communications, and marketing assets, and with QA team for technical changes, bug fixes, and client support.

### Marketing Designer, Web Developer - Element-360

Sept. 2014 - May 2016

Handled all client-branded visuals and web development including image & HTML5 ad creation, landing page campaigns, email communication design & coding, behaviour/heatmap analysis, and technical SEO auditing for 40+ national real estate communities.

Developed internal tools to facilitate SEO, campaign reporting, CRO, and user experience. Led research and testing discussion for A/B and multiviariant testing campaigns in planning & client reporting, and regularly audited performance of image/text ads and conversion rate & organic search improvements.

### **EXPERIENCE**

(continued

### **Contract UX Designer** - ThingFace

Aug. 2014 - Sept. 2014

During a two-month contract designed and prototyped an IOT app authoring web-application. With a small team, outlined the scope of the app's services, planned the implementation of the single-page front end, storyboarded the user flow, and created promotional & proof-of-concept visual assets.

### Game Artist, Animator, Video Editor - The Littlest Golfer, Inc.

Apr. 2013 - Aug. 2014

Game designer and lead artist for 2D mobile game created in Unity3D and sold on the App Store and Google Play. Created the UI, tiling environment textures, character animations spritesheets, designed puzzle-based levels, and image ads for the game release.

Additionally, worked in small team to create a 3D Animated Pilot children's show. Designed, modeled, rigged, and animated characters, handled all editing, compositing, and motion-graphics within After Effects, and created promotional print materials for the show premiere.

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Arts - New Media

Univertity of North Carolina at Asheville Concentration in 3D Animation Graduated 2012